CONTACT

hello@isaque.me

isaque.me (Portfolio)
isaque.me/linkedin (Linkedin)

TOP SKILLS

BRAND, CREATIVE, & PD STRATEGY
PRODUCT & SERVICE IDEATION
STATS & PSYCHOMETRICS
DIGITAL DESIGN • FILMMAKING • PUBLIC SPEAKING
R • SPSS • HTML/CSS • MARKETING STRATEGY

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH (NATIVE/BILINGUAL)
PORTUGUESE (NATIVE/BILINGUAL)
SPANISH (FULL PROFICIENCY)
HUNGARIAN (ELEMENTARY)
DUTCH (ELEMENTARY)

HONORS & AWARDS

2022 GLOBAL CANNES YOUNG LIONS
PBRONZE (DIGITAL)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL GOLD (FAIRPHONE)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL

** SILVER (MENTELITY FOUNDATION)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL

Key Honors (BUMA X YOUTUBE)

2021 YOUNG LIONS NL

▼ BRONZE (CONCERTGEBOUW)

HUNGARIAN HS FILM FESTIVAL

**BEST NEW FILMMAKER

AMSTERDAM MOBILITY CHALLENGE

→ SILVER (ADE)

FACAMP WEB GAME

**NATIONAL CHAMPION

2022 LIA CREATIVE LIAISONS MENTEE

PASSPORTS

BRAZILIAN

ITALIAN 💿

ISAQUE SENEDA

CREATIVE & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

SUMMARY

I am a strategist w/ product ideation, design, and consumer research skills. Brazilian w/ experience in 4 countries. I create products that tell stories because products are stories (Berkeley, 1713). In it to fix real problems. Fluent in behavioral sciences, psychometrics, and stats.

HOLLAND CODE

→ #「 ~~> ~@

ENTREPRENEURIAL • ARTISTIC • INVESTIGATIVE

CLIFTONSTRENGTHS

COMPETITION • SIGNIFICANCE • RESTORATIVE • COMMUNICATION • FOCUS

EXPERIENCE

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

PUBLICIS ITALY / LE PUB

CREATIVE & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

JUN 2021 - PRESENT (1 YEAR 6 MONTHS)

- → Joined the global Heineken account as data strategist on Data Lab;
- → Now working at Le Garage (product/tech team) as a product strategist;
- → Using deep stats to ideate innovation-led campaigns.

■ WINEPOPPER

BRAND & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

JAN 2021 - DEC 2021 (1 YEAR)

SAO PAULO, BRAZIL

- → Repositioning and rebranding of Winepopper (Brazilian gas wine opener);
- \rightarrow Managed market research, product strategy, UX & product development;
- → Sold out 200 units in a week, with launch of new website + campaign.

MUSEU DO AMANHÃ (MOTI)

DIGITAL DESIGNER & BRAND STRATEGIST NOV 2018 - JUN 2021 (2 YEARS 7 MONTHS)

- AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

 → Headed the development of FORMS' global brand identity;
- → Development of brand strategy, service strategy, and digital design.
- ightarrow FORMS: collabor. platform connecting sustainability museums worldwide.

ARENAS ESPM

ART DIRECTOR & PLANNER

FEB 2016 - JUL 2016 (6 MONTHS)

SÃO PAULO BRAZTI

- → Traineeship in ESPM student advertising agency;
- → Created campaigns for Mentos and Mondelēz Lacta BIS;
- → Collaboration with professionals from renowned agencies in São Paulo.

EDUCATION

TOTTERDAM SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT, ERASMUS UNIVERSITY

MSc, MARKETING MANAGEMENT · (2020 - 2021)

PARSONS SCHOOL OF DESIGN, THE NEW SCHOOL

STUDY ABROAD, COMMUNICATION DESIGN · (2020 - 2020)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

BSc, COMMUNICATION SCIENCE (*HONORS) · (2017 - 2020)
MINOR, BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION · (2018 - 2019)

ESCOLA SUPERIOR DE PROPAGANDA E MARKETING

PORTFOLIO SCHOOL, ARENAS ESPM · (2016 - 2016)

WILLEM DE KOONING ACADEMY

PROPEDEUSE, AUDIOVISUAL DESIGN · (2016 - 2017)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

ROTARY INTERNATIONAL

YOUTH EXCHANGE STUDENT IN HUNGARY AUG 2014 - JUL 2015 (1 YEAR)

TNW CONFERENCE

STAFF

MAY 2018 - MAY 2019 (1 YEAR)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

MEGA TABLE, FOUNDER & STATS TUTOR
OCT 2017 - PRESENT (4 YEARS 10 MONTHS)